Finding Aid for the Preston Sturges Papers LSC.1114
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Film Productions
  - Miscellaneous Scripts Written By P.S. During, 1950s
    - The McKesson Story also known as: The Metamorphosis of Philip Musica., 1958.; Typed treatment. (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Radio appearance as panelist. (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Some Of The Events Leading Up To My Death, notes dating to, 1944. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Story notes: miscellaneous. (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - The Sturges Stories, television prospectus and budget., 1951. (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Script. Suits Me Fine., February 28, 1951.; (2 copies) [Bound volume]. (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Unidentifiable script in French., June 1958. (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - A Woman's Story treatment., December 9, 1958. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous Projects
    - California Pictures Corporation., 1944-1946. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Business documents. (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Script. The Millionairess, adaptation of Bernard Shaw play., January 8, 1954.; [Bound volume]. (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Script, unidentified, H.L. Picture., (2 copies incomplete). (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Discard pages, The Good Fairy. (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous pages, The Good Fairy. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Production Materials
    - The Beautiful Blonde From Bashful Bend (). Schedule-call sheets-photocopy of production board., 1949 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - The Great McGinty (). Production reports., 1940; [Bound volume]. (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - The Great McGinty (). Photocopy of production board., 1940 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - The Great Moment. (). Production reports schedule., 1944 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Hail The Conquering Hero (). Production reports-schedule., 1944 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - I Married A Witch (). Budget., 1942; [Bound volume]. (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Mad Wednesday (). Call sheets-schedules., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Mad Wednesday, (). Bit and extra. player requisitions., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - The Miracle Of Morgan's Creek (). Production reports - photocopy of production board., 1944 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Unfaithfully Yours (). Call sheets., 1948 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Vendetta (). Call sheets-schedule., 1950 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - The Beautiful Blonde From Bashful Bend (). Crew-cast-budget-footage chart - deal slips., 1949 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Christmas In July (). Cast-crew-call sheets schedule., 1940 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - The Great McGinty (). Production script., 1940 December 1939.; [Bound volume]. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Lady Eve (). Cast-schedule-music scoring inter-office memos., 1941 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - The Palm Beach Story (). Cast-schedule inter-office memos., 1942 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - The Power and the Glory (). Participation reports schedule., 1933 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Unfaithfully Yours (). Crew-cast-budget synopsis-schedule., 1948 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Vendetta (). Cast-cost reports - inter-office memos., 1950 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Paramount: Cost comparison chart. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Paramount: Miscellaneous data. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Laugh meter and preview notes - including The Philadelphia Story. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Players Club
    - Financial correspondence, by date, including ASCAP and unpaid bills. (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Government correspondence, by date, including lawsuits and labor board. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, by date: Applications and offers. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Menus and advertising. (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Planned improvements, including sketches. (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, by date, including telegrams. (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Players Stock Company - cast and production notes. (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - The Bad Man (Incomplete) script-cast-set sketches. (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Barber Shop Blues (Incomplete) script and set plan. (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - The Boor (Sturges translation of Anto Chekhov) (Incomplete) script-set plan. (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - A Minuet script by Louis Parker & Robert Nathan (two copies-incomplete). (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - The Monkey's Paw (Incomplete) script-set plan. (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Room Service production notes. (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Room Service (Incomplete) play script Sam French edition. (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Production Material
  Arranged by Charlotte Payne.
  - The Bad Man
    - Script changes, n.p., November 2, 1951.; 5 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Beauregard The Bookworm
    - Story ideas. n.p., n.d.; 3 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - The Beautiful Blond From Bashful Bend (20th Century Fox. ), 1949
    - Contract notes, n.p., n.d.; 2 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., v.d.; 22 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence - Holloway, Sterling. n.p., 3 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Publicity. v.p., 1949.; 12 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Broadway Melody
    - Correspondence. Los Angeles., July 22, 1938.; 1 leaf. (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Outline notes by Eddie Buzzell. n.p., April 26, 1938.; 19 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Clipping., 1 item. (Box 35, Folder 8a)
  - Buccaneer (Paramount. ), 1937
    - Correspondence and credits. Los Angeles., 1937.; 3 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Carnival In Flanders
    - Correspondence. Los Angeles., 1953.; 1 leaf. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Cat Business
    - Correspondence - Hawks, Howard W. v.p., 1956.; 8 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Child Of Manhattan (Play, Produced ), 1932
    (Also known as: Consider the Lily)
    - Box office statements. v.p., 1932.; ca. 50 pieces. (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Casting notes. n.p., n.d.; 10 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Contracts: New York., 1932.; 6 items. (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence - miscellaneous. v.p., 1932.; 9 leaves. (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Script. n.p., 1931.; 2 copies. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Script notes, n.p., n.d.; 10 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Stage plan. n.p., n.d.; 1 piece. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Christmas In July (Paramount. ), 1940
    (Also known as: A Cup of Coffee)
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., v.d.; 11 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Credits. n.p., 1940.; 1 leaf. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Notes. v.p., v.d.; 7 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Publicity. v.p., 1940.; 16 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Screenplay - miscellaneous pages. n.p., ca. 1935.; 87 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Story purchase authorization. n.p., 1940.; 1 leaf. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - College Swing
    - Credits. v.p., 1937.; 3 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Story notes, n.p., n.d.; 4 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - A Connecticut Yankee In King Arthur's Court
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., 1943.; 9 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Notes. v.p., 1943.; 2 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Coronation
    - Synopsis of screenplay, incomplete. n.p., n.d.; 14 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon) with holograph corrections. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Diamond Jim (Universal. ), 1935
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., 1935.; 2 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Easy Living (Paramount. ), 1937
    - Correspondence. Los Angeles., ca. 1937.; 2 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Credits. Los Angeles., 1937.; 5 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Notes. n.p., n.d.; 1 leaf. (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Publicity. n.p., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Fanny
    (Later produced as the Port of Seven Seas)
    - Assignment. Los Angeles., 1938.; 4 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., v.d.; 4 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Fast and Loose (Paramount. ), 1930
    (Also known as: The Best People)
    - Payment. New York., July 9, 1930.; 1 leaf. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - La Femme de Boulanger
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., v.d.; 6 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Flight from Youth
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., v.d.; 3 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Frankie and Johnnie (Play, Produced ), 1929
    - Contract. New York., 1929.; 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., v.d.; 3 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Dialogue notes. n.p., ca. 1929.; 5 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Publicity brochure., 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 24a)
  - The French They Are a Funny Race (SNE Gaumont. ), 1957
    (Also known as: Les Carnets du Major Thompson)
    - Correspondence - General. v.p., 1954-1957; (In 3 folders)
      - 11 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - 10 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - 10 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Notes. v.p., v.d.; 13 items. (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - The Gentleman from Chicago
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., 1955-1958.; 14 pieces. (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - ---. Balcon, Sir Michael. v.p., 1957.; 9 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence - Donen, Stanley., 1958.; 7 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - ---. Freeman, Y. Frank., 1957.; 2 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 32)
    - ---. Girosi, Marcello., 1955-1957.; 15 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 33)
    - ---. Henaghan, James., 1957.; 5 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 34)
    - ---. Joseph, Rudolph., 1957-1958.; 11 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 35)
    - ---. Karp, Jacob., 1959.; 8 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 36)
    - ---. Larsen, Niels., 1957.; 8 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 37)
    - ---. Lawrence, Marc., 1957.; 4 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 38)
    - ---. Reade, Walter., 1957.; 7 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 39)
    - ---. Scott, Raymond., 1959.; 2 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 40)
    - ---. Shepridge, John., 1957.; 2 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 41)
    - ---. Winikus, Francis., 1958.; 5 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 42)
    - ---. Youngstein, Max E., 1957.; 7 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 43)
    - Script notes, n.p., March 30, 1958.; 10 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections and holograph. (Box 36, Folder 44)
  - The Golden Fleecing
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., 1958-1959.; 4 pieces. (Box 36, Folder 45)
    - Notes, n.p., n.d.; 4 items. (Box 36, Folder 46)
  - The Good Fairy (Universal. ), 1935
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., v.d.; 5 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 47)
    - Dialogue notes. n.p., 1934.; 5 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 48)
  - The Great Hugo
    - Correspondence - general. n.p., 1953.; 2 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 49)
    - Notes for screenplay. n.p., 1953.; 26 leaves. (Box 36, Folder 50)
  - The Great McGinty (Paramount. ), 1940
    - Agreement, n.p., 1939.; 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Cast and crew. v.p., v.d.; In 4 folders. (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., 1938-1959.; 18 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - ---. Crowther, Bosley. New York., 1946.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - ---. Dozier, William., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - ---. Freeman, Y. Frank., 1957.; 8 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - ---. Henigson, Henry., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - ---. Hornblow, Arthur, Jr., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - ---. Karp, Jacob H., 1959.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - ---. Kohner, Paul., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - ---. Leborg, Reginald., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - ---. Mannix, Edgar., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - ---. Meyer, Fred S., 1935.; 2 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - ---. Ruben, Albert., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - ---. Skouras, Spyros P., 1941.; 5 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Notes - general. n.p., n.d.; 4 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Premier. Los Angeles., 1940.; 6 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Publicity, v.p., 1940.; 14 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - ---., 10 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - ---., 10 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 23)
    - ---., 9 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 24)
    - ---., 10 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 25)
    - ---., 10 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - ---., 15 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - ---., 3 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Production notes. v.p., v.d.; 10 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Wardrobe. n.p., n.d.; 9 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - ---., 9 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 31)
  - The Great Moment (Paramount. ), 1944
    (Also known as: Triumph Over Pain)
    - Audience response cards., 1942.; 9 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Budget., 1942.; 11 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 33)
    - Call sheets., 1942.; 6 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 34)
    - Cast and crew., 1942.; 8 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 35)
    - Censorship., 1942.; 6 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., 1942-1946.; 9 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 37)
    - ---., 10 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 38)
    - ---., 9 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 39)
    - ---. De Casseres, Benjamin., 1944.; 6 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 40)
    - ---. DeSylva, B.G., 1942-1944.; 9 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 41)
    - ---. Freeman, Y. Frank., 1942-1944.; 5 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 42)
    - ---. Fuelop-Miller, Rene., 1941-1942.; 3 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 43)
    - ---. Gordon, Ruth., n.d.; 1 leaf. (Box 37, Folder 44)
    - ---. Research correspondence., 1939-1943.; 10 items. (Box 37, Folder 45)
    - ---., 9 items. (Box 37, Folder 46)
    - ---., 10 items. (Box 37, Folder 47)
    - ---. 7 items. (Box 37, Folder 48)
    - Notes, v.p., v.d.; 7 items. (Box 37, Folder 49)
    - ---., 11 items. (Box 37, Folder 50)
    - Production notes., 1942.; 10 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 51)
    - Prologue. v,p., 1942.; 10 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 52)
    - ---., 10 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 53)
    - ---., 14 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 54)
    - Publicity., 2 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 55)
    - Research material. v.p., v.d. (Box 37)
      - Article, n.p., n.d.; 35 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 37, Folder 56)
      - Published articles and pamphlets., 10 items. (Box 37, Folder 57)
      - Miscellaneous., 16 pieces. (Box 37, Folder 58)
    - Shooting schedule., 1942.; 15 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 59)
    - Synopsis., n.d.; 2 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 60)
    - Title suggestions., 1942-1943.; 10 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 61)
    - ---., 10 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 62)
    - ---., 5 leaves. (Box 37, Folder 63)
  - The Guinea Pig (Play, Produced ), 1929
    (Also know as: Passion Preferred)
    - Arbitration, New York., 1929.; 9 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Box office statements. v.p., 1929.; 16 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Contract. New York., 1929.; 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence., 8 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - ---., 1928.; 7 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - ---., 1929.; 10 leaves in each of 5 folders. (Box 38, Folder 6-10)
    - ---., 1929-1931.; 10 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - ---., 1931-1946.; 7 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Notes. v.p., v.d.; 11 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Programs and publicity, v.p., 1929.; 14 items. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Properties. New York., 1930.; 2 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Screenplay - miscellaneous pages. n.p., n.d.; 5 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Speech by Preston Sturges. n.p., n.d.; 3 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Stock shares and agreements. New York., 1929.; 4 items. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Hail the Conquering Hero (Paramount. ), 1944
    - Correspondence - general. v.p., 1944-1945.; 10 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 19)
    - ---., 10 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 20)
    - ---., 7 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 21)
    - ---. Freeman, Y. Frank. n.p., 1944.; 2 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 22)
    - ---. Nichols, Dudley. Los Angeles., 1944.; 1 leaf. (Box 38, Folder 23)
    - Publicity., 1944.; 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 24)
    - Titles and notes. n.p., 10 items. (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Hotbed (Play, Produced ), 1928
    - Contract. New York., 1928.; 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Hotel Haywire (Paramount. ), 1937
    - Production notes. Los Angeles., 1937.; 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - I Belong To Zozo
    (Also known as: J'appartiens a Zozo)
    - Agreement., 1957-1959.; 3 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence - General., 1957-1959
      - Correspondence., 1957.; 11 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - ---., 13 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - ---., 14 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Correspondence., 1958.; 11 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - ---., 11 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - ---., 10 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - ---., 9 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Correspondence., 1959.; 10 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - ---., 10 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 37)
      - ---., 6 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Notes., 1956-1958.; 6 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 39)
    - Screenplay - incomplete., 1958.; 21 leaves. Typescript. (Box 38, Folder 40)
  - I Married a Witch (United Artists. ), 1942
    - Agreement., 1941.; 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 41)
  - I Spy
    - Correspondence., 1943.; 2 leaves. (Box 38, Folder 42)
  - The Invisible Man (Universal. ), 1932
    - Correspondence., 1932.; 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 43)
  - June Noon
    - Production notes., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 44)
  - Khaki-Whacky
    - Title note., 1942.; 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 45)
  - The Lady Eve (Paramount. ), 1941
    - Correspondence - general., 1941.; 6 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - ---. Deane, Albert., 1941.; 19 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - ---. Lachman, Harry., 1941.; 1 leaf. (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - ---. Lewin, Albert., 1938-1939.; 12 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - ---. Zanuck, Darryl., 1941.; 3 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Publicity - South America., 2 scrapbooks (in 2 folders). (Box 39, Folder 6-7)
    - Publicity - United States., 17 items. (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Screenplay eliminations., n.d.; 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Reviews. v.p., v.d.; 80 items. (Box 39, Folder 9a)
  - Life Behind the Eight Ball
    - Story notes., n.d.; 1 leaf. Typescript. (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Title notes., 1943.; 3 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - The Life of Riley
    - Correspondence., 1938.; 3 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Long Live the King
    - Correspondence - Larsen, Niels., 1956.; 4 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Love in the Afternoon
    - Correspondence - general., 1942.; 3 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Story idea., n.d.; 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Lux Radio Theater. Los Angeles., 1945
    - Contract., 1945.; 6 items. (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Production notes., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Script., 1945.; 46 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Script framework., 1945.; 16 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Madison Avenue Story
    - Notes., 1959.; 2 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Make a Wish
    - Correspondence., 1954-1955.; 10 leaves. (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Matrix
    - Agreement and assignment of rights., 1946-1947.; 4 items. (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - general., 1933-1958.; 10 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - ---. Abramson, Charles., 1951-1956.; 12 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - ---. Girosi, Marcello., 1957.; 6 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - ---. Zanuck, Darryl., 1947.; 4 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Notes., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Screenplay (Incomplete), ca. 1950.; 22 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Story
      - Original screen story. n.p., November 22, 1933.; 27 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Screen story (Incomplete), September 9, 1949.; 2 leaves. Typescript. (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Screen story (Incomplete), September 18, 1949.; 19 leaves. Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Screen story (Incomplete), n.d.; 7 leaves. Typescript. (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Screen story. Plan of procedure (Incomplete), October 9, 1949.; 1 leaf. (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Screen story. Discarded pages., n.d.; 7 leaves. Typescript and typescript (carbon). (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Synopsis. A woman's story., 1958.; 9 leaves. Typescript (carbon). (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - The Millionairess and Three Black Pennies
    - Agreement. London., 1954.; 1 item. (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence., 1953.; 10 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - ---., 1954.; 10 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - ---., 1954.; 11 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - ---., 1954.; 12 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - ---., n.d.; 3 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Notes. n.p., 1953.; 9 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - The Miracle of Morgan's Creek (Paramount. ), 1944
    - Cast and crew., 1942.; 15 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Censorship., 1942-1943.; 10 pieces in each of 3 folders. (Box 40, Folder 23-25)
    - ---., 7 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Contract., September 11, 1942.; 1 item. (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence., 1942-1943.; 11 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence., 1944
    - ---., 10 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence., 1944.; 11 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - ---., 11 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - ---., 10 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - ---., 10 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - ---., 11 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - ---., 7 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 35)
    - Credits., 1942.; 2 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 36)
    - Notes., ca. 1942.; 6 leaves. (Box 40, Folder 37)
    - Production notes., 1942-1943.; 10 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 38)
    - ---., 16 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 39)
    - Publicity., 1944.; 12 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 40)
    - Shooting schedule., 1942.; 16 pieces. (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - Moonbirds
    (Also known as: Les Oiseaux de lune)
    - Correspondence., 1958-1959.; 3 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Murder Without Crime
    - Correspondence.- Larsen, Niels., 1957.; 11 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Leiser, Henri., 1957.; 9 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Musica Story
    Projected film of the biography of Philip Musica.
    - Agreement., 1957.; 3 leaves. (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence., 1957-1958.; 10 pieces in each of 6 folders. (Box 41, Folder 5-10)
    - ---., 12 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Research. Clipped article by Robert Shaplen., 12 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Synopses and story notes., 9 pieces. Typescript (carbon) and holograph. (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - New York Town (Paramount. ), 1941
    - Correspondence., 1941.; 1 piece. (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Nothing Doing
    (Also known as: Mr. Big in Littleville)
    - Correspondence., 1949-1951.; 3 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Notes., 1949.; 4 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Palm Beach Story (Paramount. ), 1942
    (Also known as: Is that Bad?)
    - Censorship., 1941.; 3 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Notes., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Previews., 1942; 2 items. (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Story rights., 1941.; 3 items. (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Le Papillon
    - Story notes., 1945.; 5 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Paris Holiday
    - Salary., 1957.; 1 item. (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Percy the Parson
    - Correspondence., 1956-1957.; 4 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - The Power and the Glory (Fox. ), 1933
    - Awards., 1933.; 1 item. (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence - general., 1933.; 3 items. (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence - Zanuck, Darryl., 1957-1958.; 5 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 26)
    - Notes., n.d.; 1 item. Holograph. (Box 41, Folder 27)
    - Screenplay (Incomplete), n.d.; 1 leaf. Typescript (carbon). (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Praise the Lord and Pass the Ammunition
    - Assignment., 1943.; 1 leaf. (Box 41, Folder 29)
    - Screenplay (Incomplete)., 1 leaf. Typescript. (Box 41, Folder 30)
    - Story notes., 1943.; 1 leaf. Typescript. (Box 41, Folder 31)
    - Title., 1943.; 2 leaves. (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - A Prevalence of Witches
    - Correspondence., 1958.; 5 leaves. (Box 41, Folder 33)
  - Recapture (Play, Produced ), 1930
    - Correspondence., 1929-1931.; 3 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 34)
    - Programs and reviews., 4 items. (Box 41, Folder 35)
  - Remember the Night (Paramount. ), 1940
    - Titles., 1939.; 3 pieces. (Box 41, Folder 36)
  - Revolt of the Women